Hi, in the previous lesson, we already created the full development plan for our currency converter application in Cursor
The plan includes everything we need the structure UI, logic, data, some improvements
And now we will also execute the entire plan automatically and generate the first version of our application
So what Cursor will do? Cursor will build them by step according to the plan
I will switch to the preview, you can also switch between markdown and preview
And just a few words, you can edit your plan, if you'd like, you can delete something, you can type
If you'd like, you can also copy paste my plan from resources in just paste right here
instead of this one, just switch to the markdown
And it will build a mouse mine
So Cursor will do it step-by-step by this one
If you don't like it at all, we can always stop it and then ask build again from scratch
So the plan is ready, we just need to click build, I will click build and allow Cursor to build it
So Cursor will create some files, some components, features in our project
We just also yet not exist, but it will appear in a moment
So what else? When the execution finished, we can review all the code and test that application works
And if something will be wrong, we can ask Cursor to fix some parts of the code
or the plan, so it can do it
As you see, it starts from creating an application
Yeah, we have now an application folder, it starts from the package the JSON file
But you need to install the project, I hope you'll do it, you have the commands
Okay, yeah, but let's wait, anyway
Now better what we do
Okay, yeah
You see, Cursor's folder was created, so maybe he created folders
One by one, because when we use wheat, we normally generate everything at once
I just download the kind of template, but Cursor do it, one by one might be
Already not having a boilerplate called here, so it is great, that also can work for us
So what is important to say, I want to review it one more time
Your application structure can be different from mine because
AI is generative, so it cannot
Outset, every request generates a data based on a knowledge, so with a really small chance, you generate the same data or the same response
So don't worry, if your application looks different
as many days to show you the approach, how to build an application
And you can build any application with by this approach
So that you know, what is it, how to use a plan mode, how to build with a plan, how to make some adjustments to the plan, how to
Ask about some feature improvements, of course, how to fix errors with Cursor, yeah, so it's the main goal
Yeah, but you can always look at my plan at my application, how is it built?
I will share the, I think I will share the code repository where you can check
everyone has some sources, code sources and see how it works in mine application
So let's wait, your ability, it's of course required some time, but we can already review some components
We have any amount, input, we have currencies, so it's really smart to split it up on components
But I would say, the first time I would build a draft version, it didn't suggest me to move it as separate components
It might be hula or something from it, might be because of a use auto model, use smarter model
Like I know clouds on that and build it much better with architecture approach, so I don't know
to be honest, but every time we get a new result
Okay, we see it created more data, we have also the result, the just paragraph which is the result
and format, it's really smart to split it up, we have also the slope button, we have our currencies
These of currencies, we use names and we use emojis of the black countries
We also have our rate, it's uploaded to values for the rate
Oh, okay, we have our main application, where we use all our components, it's really clean structure
I would say, we have styles, a lot of styles, it's fine
And the main file we have, we have just this direct application
So, okay, from now we don't use any different packages, we use just TypeScript, we then drag them, it's okay
Okay, let's check, I think we'll sort of finish to build an application
Uh, yes, he marked all item is done, so we can open a terminal, we already did the review of the code
I first we need to open our application, I go to the currency converter app, I hope the penances are installed
I will try to, yeah, run def, just run application, no, come on, not found, so I see him can need
to install all the dependencies first, he did not hit, but he should, we mentioned he will check it
Okay, now I can run the application
have it to work, cannot run package with like in a hierarchy, but what's going on?
Okay, uh, error model not found, I think something's going wrong, so I can copy paste the
error to the chart
All right, doesn't have the paste, yeah, okay, you see it was pasted and run application
So, let's allow cursor to investigate it, maybe it's some stupid error, I don't know what
it tried to install the penances, mention I just want to run an app, let's pull, and fix in the
start up at all, but I didn't miss and react again, okay, I think Coresort did mistake when he
installed, when he didn't use with to install an application, he it generates and files one by one,
maybe it was more difficult, but let's see, if you still see, should try, clean the with cache,
oh, let's run an payment install again, let's install a new dependency, and use them on dev,
yeah, now it works, so we can run an application in browser, we have a beautiful currency converter,
let's try to convert one door to, I guess it's rupee, oh, we have it, let's maybe choose euro
and if it choose USD, yeah, it's same, so we can, let's choose, so we can do swap, you see it works,
we can use bigger amounts, it even promoted with commerce, now it's fine, I guess it's fine for the
first version of our application, and in the next version we will improve it step by step,
and see you!